

im.mahirmersimoski@gmail.c



076597008



North Macedonia



linkedin.com/in/mahirmersimoski



github.com/mersimoski

SKILLS

ReactJS

HTML

Handling REST API

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Macedonian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Albanian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

MERN Stack

Redesigning, Updating, Optimizing and making mobile & user friendly Websites.

Mahir Mersimoski

Cool Software Developer

Professional googler with over 2y experience in building Advanced and Dynamic websites and web apps. Gentleman off-desk but nerd in-desk doing what it takes to satisfy the user experience, client needs and deliver services on time.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Ultrasoft

10/2021 - Present

Content Management products for Swiss clients

Strapi, React 18, Redux, Functional Components, REST API, Javascript, HTML, CSS, TailwindCSS

Member

digicube North Macedonia

02/2021 - 10/2021

Using their office, working with their partner.

Software Developer

Newsroom Technologies AG

02/2021 - 10/2021

Live Stream and Membership web

WordPress, Elementor, Dynamic Content, Custom Fields, React JS Redux, HTML, CSS

WordPress Developer & Community Manager

Pro Option Trader

10/2020 - 01/2021 WordPress, BuddyBoss, Memberpress, PHP Social platform for Traders

CERTIFICATES

First Place in a Programming Tournament in Bitola, Macedonia (03/2017 - 03/2017)

PROJECTS

Event scheduler and membership web app for a huge Swiss dentist association

https://parodontologie.ch

Trading Social Network, FaceBook-like platform for Traders

http://prooptiontrader.com/

Bern Congress Organization - Web application for scheduling live events

https://www.bern-co.com/

https://qithub.com/mersimoski (most of the repositories are private, company policy)

https://caymland.com/ - https://ultrasoft.mk/ - parodontologie.ch/- maksutoska.at/ - laboratoriosbabe.mk/ - www.captainwords.com - https://aaipa.gov.mk - homeworkouts101.com - bonsaialchemist.com easywaybaby.com - kulstudios.com/ - efp.osteology.org - electro-tec-digital.ch - www.vks-fachtagung.ch tcs-livestream.ch/

EDUCATION

Dropout Computer Science and Engineering UIST Paul the Apostle

08/2019 - 08/2020

Ohrid, Macedonia

Courses

Focused on self teaching instead.